[Music]
she Nevers
word that's a pretty voice ins and
compy yes you tell
[Applause]
you we Le it the same
time
yeah
to to me help
me me
everything
she
we around
[Music]
by she the
angel come
around yeah
yeah come
around don't you know that
[Music]
be woo
oh four Shar
[Applause]
baby of the
rain the falls upon your
skin it's closer than my
hands oh I'm jealous of the
[Music]
rain so wish
you the best
of all this world would give and I've
always thought you come back tell me oh
you found
what heart
breaking it's hard for me to say I'm
jelling so the way you're happy without
me cuz I wish
you the best
of all this world would give and I
always thought you come back tell me oh
you found
wi
heartbreaking misery
it's hard for me to say I'm jealous of
the way you're happy without
[Applause]
[Music]
me NE
for y
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
foree
for
sh
[Music]
[Applause]
wish I
could I could have say
[Applause]
goodbye I
[Music]
wanted
May for
you if
[Music]
[Applause]
I trying to
SA
want to feel
another to
[Applause]
[Music]
another off my lips don't want to get my
heart
away the
strer let another
won't never let the
sunlight no I never
love I don't want to know
[Music]
this
I for
you want to feel
another
want
to
fire to know another
kiss baby is the all
your no
[Applause]
[Music]
I
I see
trees half
green bre Roes
to I see
down for
me and I feel to
myself
What a
Wonderful
[Music]
World Sky of
FL and clouds so
white the bright BL
day the dark sa light and I feel to
myself
[Applause]
[Music]
What a
Wonderful
[Applause]
[Music]
World the colors of the
rainbow so pretty in the
sky and also down the
phases our people grounded by I see
friend Shing
High say said how do you
do they really
say I love you I hear babies
cry and I watch them
grow they Le much more that I never ever
know and I feel into
myself
What a
Wonderful
[Music]
World Class it was just
a
list
to feel super tight
Clover
[Music]
mother see you
shine it's
[Music]
your
oh you slow
[Applause]
down
[Music]
your
[Applause]
oh got
got
know
[Music]
[Applause]
you oh yeah your
[Music]
[Applause]
golden mommy don't know Daddy's get at
the something
Unholy oh I really
[Applause]
married like she kick you
if all the best that you tell me that
you
do and dirty
dir you know everybody's talking on the
SC I hear the thees that you
and keep your bus
CLE don't
Dy at sh doing something
unho
sheing
she'll and
[Applause]
ity he always call me cuz never
no getting hot getting hot body shot
body shot something
Unholy
[Applause]
[Music]
Unholy
holy
he don't know Daddy's get at The Body
Shop doing something
Unholy
[Music]
and a
night
that Beau for love
[Music]
[Applause]
say
love now always
[Music]
well
I house on L on for
[Music]
[Applause]
love
[Music]
I
I I don't
[Applause]
[Music]
need
love
[Music]
offy
oh Father tell
me do we
get what we
Des oh do we get what we
deserve and we down we
go till it down we
go
oh you let your feet run
wide time is come as we
all wow go
down cuz they will run you down down
till you
go so you can't cool no more now and way
down we
go
till we down we
go you we down we
go
wo cuz they will run you down down till
you go all we down we
[Music]
go
yeah yeah oh all way down we
go yeah we
[Music]
down yeah way down we
[Applause]
[Music]
go said I thought I was the only
one sh me you call your number one
I told I was the one why did you leave
me on so
long don't you said to
me did you even notice that I don't call
you
anymore oh did
you that I don't you
you
[Music]
see
oh oh
oh this is hard for me to
say but I'm going to say it
anyway I
[Applause]
[Music]
fall
also this is hard for me to
say but I'm going to say it
anyway I've fallen out of love with you
[Music]
for
spee
foreign
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
fore
there's no time time for
us there's no place for
us who wants to live
forever what is this thing that builds
our
dreams yet slips away from
[Music]
us who wants to live
forever who wants to live
forever
[Music]
yeah Dar
to
Forever
[Applause]
touch my
[Music]
tears with your
lipss touch my
heart when your
fingertips who want to live
forever
who want to live
forever it's our
today who Waits forever and
Away
listen to this song
here in
my
[Music]
has this song from deep
within it's only
beginning to
find
Rel oh that time has come for Mountain
we
I'm
Shadow into
your cuz you
listen
[Music]
oh
my and
I see on my mind you should
have now I don't believe in you you
don't know what I feel I world you made
me I the words you think you came to
[Music]
me
foree
[Music]
spee
[Applause]
[Music]
fore
they can
[Music]
[Applause]
get
W Ro
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
us
[Applause]
[Music]
go w
[Applause]
I'm going to start
today and you got me
[Music]
like what you want from
me and try to buy a pretty all the price
to
High baby you got me
like you love when I fall
aart so you can put me together and
throw me against the
wall baby you got me
like don't you stop Ling me don't quit
me just start Ling it
babe and babe I'm F fine with fire just
to get close to you can we burn some
babe and I R for Miles just to get a
taste Must Be Love on the
brain yeah that's got me feeling this
way it beats me black and blue but it
bus me so good and I can't get enough M
Be Love on the
[Applause]
r keep curs in my
name no matter what I do I'm no good
without you
[Music]
and
foree
o w
[Music]
spee
[Applause]
wow o
[Music]
wo
ooor
[Applause]
[Music]
foree
[Applause]
[Music]
me B me
ony
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
[Music]
see
speee
spee
[Applause]
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
[Music]
me
me the
VIS
see
[Music]
[Applause]
byee
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
foreign
spee
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
[Music]
fore
for
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
[Music]
for
[Applause]
that
[Music]
traveling in the
[Applause]
FR every
TR
I met a strange
lady she made me nervous wow she took me
in she gave me breakfast beautiful wow
she said do you come from a land down
under wom glow
plunder I love his
[Applause]
voice better
better
[Music]
take
[Applause]
[Music]
m a slack Jordan but not much to
say I said to the man trying to tempt me
ooh because I come from the land
of do you come from a land down
under
ah where we me glow and Men
[Music]
plunder that
Thunder better run than you better take
cover
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
fore
[Music]
for for
spee
[Music]
[Applause]
spee
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
not
spee
[Music]
fore
foree
[Applause]
[Music]
you
spee wo
[Music]
ah waking in the
Reel walking over
glass neighbor
[Music]
say that is
name stranger
g Who and dispers
be shield and know me at all
today from the Fain light I fly rise
like
[Applause]
[Music]
a shall give
award once I'm trans
[Music]
I Rise up to the
SK you me
down I'm going to
[Applause]
[Music]
fly of the can rise like your
feel but you're
[Music]
[Applause]
my there goes my
heartbeat in and you are the
reason I'm losing my St wow please come
back
now if I can turn
make dark spend every hour all every day
keeping you
safe and I Climb Every
Mountain and I swim every
ocean just to be with
you and fix what I'm
broken cuz I need you to
see then you are the
[Music]
res you are the
re
oh I need you to hold me
tonight I Climb Every
Mountain and stream every
[Music]
oan cuz you are the
reason there
is a house in New morning
they call the
Rising
Sun and it's been a
ruin of many a poor
boy and God I
know I'm
[Music]
one my
mother
was a tor
she Su my new blue
[Music]
jeans
[Applause]
[Music]
my can't
in
mother
not to do what I have
done spend your life in sin and
misery and a House of the
Rising
[Music]
Sun than your life and S and
misery in the heart House of the
Rising
[Applause]
[Music]
son
[Applause]
[Music]
fore
for
[Music]
[Applause]
foree
[Music]
[Applause]
speee
[Music]
thr FR
away thr the find away at all but never
go so iess I got
stand I hope
Som I
[Music]
may here even if he takes all night all
our
H days need a place to H but but I can't
f
one what I feel
alive
oh I can find my
[Music]
faith all
alone me to my mind the St take me the
PES
SK h
[Music]
welcome
home W you all the
time looking for a better place
ah something's
[Music]
on I
make
here even if he Tak all
night pleas too hard but I keep for want
near what I feel
alive
outside I can't find my
face
oh yeah
yeah
[Music]
oh for
foro
[Music]
home
[Applause]
woo I don't want to
go but baby we both
know this is not a
Time It's Time to Say
Goodbye until we meet again okay cuz if
this is not the end
it will come a
day when we will find a
way vience pain in the
Angels when the stars
are
[Applause]
be
to I
[Music]
don't suck me
like I
[Music]
don't I
want o I don't care about
[Music]
[Applause]
that
if
[Applause]
you it ain't no
[Music]
[Applause]
way for me to give you all you
need if you won't let me give you all of
[Music]
me I know that a woman's
duty is to help and lo a
man and that's the way you was
play
[Music]
i oh but how can I how can
I give you all the things
iast if your timeing both on my
hands
oh it ain't no
way it ain't no
[Music]
way just ain't no way
baby it ain't no way
[Music]
baby it ain't no
[Applause]
[Music]
way man
the
hood what
what
oh
oh oh yeah wow
[Music]
wow
foree
[Music]
B
[Applause]
[Music]
s my
[Applause]
love oh
wowow
10 three and I'm Waking Up In Your
[Music]
[Applause]
Arms skin on
skin nothing else
[Music]
Ms oh will been here for a
while haven't seen the sun come
[Music]
out oh we've been loving and
silence driving with our
bodies I feel like running again
oh I want to do it again
again I feel like I'm running
again
okay I want to do it
again I feel like
running again
[Music]
[Applause]
and I'm wake it up in your
[Music]
arms on
skin nothing
else
[Music]
matter looking out on the morning
rain I used to feel so
[Music]
uninspired and when I knew I had to face
another day Lord you make me feel so
tired before the day I met
you life was so kind but you're the key
to my pce of
my You Make Me
Feel You Make Me
Feel You make me feel like a natural
woman
oh baby what you done to
me and I just want to
be close to you you make me feel
so oh
make me
feel make me feel you make me feel like
a
natural
oh make me feel you make me
feel you might feel like a
natural
[Music]
warm and I am
you
wow and you're the best of me I love
know there's no
reaction go no there's no
way there no way I am living without you
I am not living without
you
want to be
free I'm
stay
[Music]
[Applause]
stay I am not out stop all the who
strike can't kill I'm not going to leave
you this
tonight and the best ever know that's
the way I
could know are living without you I'm
not living without you I'm not living
without
you you
[Applause]
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
oh El
for
spe
spee
for
[Music]
spe
[Applause]
for
I
[Music]
we can take a photo turn light this
moment for the days when I don't believe
when I love gets stolen there's no
exception that no time will take
[Applause]
[Music]
you
[Applause]
right beside the lake I burn for you you
burned for
me so kiss me the
way that you
would if we die
tonight come on owe me the way yeah that
you would for the final
times and
Whatever May Come somewhere deep inside
there's always this verion of you and I
so just kiss me the way that you
would if we die
tonight all the deepest Secrets all the
darkest moments oh I promise there
be inv my L you are I want to
breathe come
on what beside the lake I burn for you
you burn from
me woo come on so kiss me the way that
you
would if we die
tonight and hold me the way that you
would for the final
times would ever make
somewhere deep inside there's always
this verion of you and that so just kiss
me the
way if we die tonight if we die
[Music]
[Applause]
tonight
[Music]
[Applause]
fore
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
Fore
foree
[Music]
[Applause]
to get back
home there was a way
beautiful so get back
home do not
cry and I will
[Music]
[Applause]
sing
SL your
eyes yes
small you you
[Applause]
and I will
sing wow so
beautiful to get back home
World
hey once through was a
[Music]
way to get back
[Applause]
[Music]
oh keep
[Applause]
me
delighted
m